HEY.
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
JOEY HAS BEEN
HOLDING HIS BREATH
FOR ALMOST FOUR MINUTES.
DUDE, ARE YOU TRYING TO KILL ME?
PHEEBS.
I WANT TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
UH-HUH. WHAT?
WELL, SINCE
I'M MOVING OUT
AN-AND YOU'RE
SO BEAUTIFUL..
OH...
HOW ABOUT
I MOVE IN WITH YOU?
WELL, THAT WOULD BE GREAT
BUT THEN WHAT DO WE DO
ABOUT DENISE?
WHO'S DENISE?
MY ROOMMATE.
DO YOU HAVE A ROOMMATE?
YES, DENISE. DENISE.
WHAT IS WITH
THE SECRECY, PHOEBE?
AND WHAT ABOUT THIS DENISE?
IS SHE CUTE?
PHEEBS, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
HOW CAN YOU HAVE A ROOMMATE
NONE OF US KNOW ABOUT?
MAYBE BECAUSE YOU NEVER LISTEN
TO ANYTHING THAT I SAY.
I TALK ABOUT HER ALL THE TIME.
DENISE!
Joey:
HEY, RACHE, LISTEN...
I WAS THINKING, UH,
I'M GOING TO HAVE
AN EXTRA ROOM
OVER AT MY PLACE.
OH, THAT'S TRUE.
YEAH, WHY DON'T YOU
MOVE IN WITH ME?
WE CAN, LIKE, STAY UP
LATE TALKING AND WATCH MOVIES...
AND YOU KNOW
ABOUT NAKED THURSDAYS, RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH, I THINK I'M
GOING TO FIND MY OWN PLACE.
HEY, HEY!
I THOUGHT NAKED THURSDAYS
WAS JUST OUR THING, MAN.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY.
HI.
SO WHAT DID
RACHEL SAY
WHEN YOU TOLD HER YOU
WERE STILL MARRIED TO HER?
OH, THAT. UM...
SHE TOOK IT REALLY WELL.
OH. YOU DIDN'T TELL
HER, DID YOU?
NO.
OF COURSE NOT, BECAUSE
YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH HER.
I AM NOT IN
LOVE WITH HER.
SHE WAS VERY UPSET
ABOUT HAVING TO MOVE OUT
SO I-I DIDN'T TELL HER
WE WERE STILL MARRIED
'CAUSE SHE'D ONLY
GET MORE UPSET.
I-I-I JUST, I
COMFORTED HER
AS A FRIEND.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
COMFORTED HER?
IT WAS NOTHING,
JUST GAVE HER A HUG.
UH-HUH! A CLASSIC
SIGN OF LOVE, THE HUG.
IT'S ALSO A SIGN
OF FRIENDSHIP.
YEAH, NOT IN YOUR CASE,
LOVEY LOVERSON.
IT WAS A HUG.
ALL RIGHT, JUST
TELL ME THIS.
DID YOU OR DID YOU NOT
SMELL HER HAIR?
S-SM-SMELL HER HAIR?
WELL, WHAT IF I DID?
90% OF A WOMAN'S PHEROMONES
COME OUT THE TOP OF HER HEAD.
THAT'S WHY,
THAT'S WHY WOMEN ARE SHORTER.
SO THAT MEN WILL FALL
IN LOVE WHEN THEY HUG THEM.
OH, COME ON, ROSS,
YOU'RE A SCIENTIST.
I WAS HUGGING HER
AS A FRIEND, OKAY.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT HER,
HER HAIR GOT IN MY FACE.
SHE'S GOT A LOT OF IT
AND IT SMELLS
ALL, ALL, UH...
( inhales )
YOU KNOW, COCONUTTY.
WHAT? OH--
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I
HAVE FEELINGS FOR RACHEL.
MAYBE IT MEANS I HAVE
FEELINGS FOR COCONUTS.
OKAY. WHATEVER YOU SAY
BUT JUST BE CAREFUL,
ALL RIGHT?
RACHEL'S NOT
IN THE SAME PLACE YOU ARE.
OKAY, IF THE PLACE
YOU'RE REFERRING TO
IS BEING IN LOVE
THEN SHE IS IN THE
SAME PLACE AS ME
BECAUSE I AM NOT
IN THAT PLACE.
OKAY, I DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND THAT
BUT, YOU KNOW
MAYBE THAT'S 'CAUSE
YOU WERE SPEAKING
THE SECRET LANGUAGE OF LOVE.
HEY.
HI.
DUDE, SOME GUY
JUST CALLED FOR YOU.
WHO WAS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ABOUT, "THANKS
FOR TAKING THE MESSAGE"? GEEZ.
HEY, LISTEN,
YOU KNOW
WHEN YOU MOVE IN,
RACHEL'S ROOM'S
GOING TO BE EMPTY.
YOU WANT
TO TALK ABOUT
WHAT WE WANT
TO DO WITH IT?
SURE.
OKAY. I WAS THINKING
WE SHOULD HAVE
A BEAUTIFUL
GUEST ROOM, RIGHT?
WITH A MAHOGANY SLEIGH BED
AND BEDSIDE TABLES
WITH FLOWERS ON IT ALL THE TIME
AND THEN WE CAN HAVE
A ROLL-TOP DESK
WITH LITTLE COMMENT CARDS
SO PEOPLE
CAN TELL US HOW MUCH
THEY LOVED
STAYING HERE.
OR WHATEVER, YOU KNOW.
I REALLY HAVEN'T THOUGHT
ABOUT IT MUCH.
WELL, I LIKE THAT
IDEA. OBVIOUSLY.
BUT I WAS THINKING MAYBE,
MAYBE... MAYBE IT COULD BE
A GAME ROOM, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, YOU CAN BUY
OLD ARCADE GAMES
LIKE, UH, LIKE SPACE INVADERS
AND ASTEROIDS FOR $200.
THE REAL ONES,
THE BIG, BIG, BIG ONES.
NO.
OKAY, SO YOU MEAN "NO"
AS IN, "GEE, CHANDLER,
WHAT AN INTERESTING IDEA
LET'S DISCUSS IT BEFORE
WE REJECT IT COMPLETELY."
OH, I'M SORRY. OF COURSE.
YES, INTERESTING IDEA.
TALK ABOUT IT, BUT... NO.
SO THAT'S IT?
I JUST DON'T THINK THAT,
YOU KNOW, ARCADE GAMES
GO IN THE BEAUTIFUL GUEST ROOM.
THE BEAUTIFUL
GUEST ROOM'S
GOING TO BE FILLED
WITH ANTIQUES.
WHICH IS WHY
ASTEROIDS IS PERFECT.
IT'S THE OLDEST GAME.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE AGAINST
THE BEAUTIFUL GUEST ROOM?
NOTHING. I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
AGAINST THE BEAUTIFUL GUEST ROOM
ESPECIALLY SINCE
EVERYBODY THAT WE KNOW
LIVES ABOUT 30 SECONDS AWAY.
ARE YOU MOCKING ME?
NO, I'M NOT MOCKING YOU
OR YOUR "BEAUTIFUL GUEST ROOM."
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
OH, NOTHING. MONICA AND
I HAD A STUPID FIGHT.
BUT YOU'RE STILL MOVING IN
TOGETHER, RIGHT?
'CAUSE MY AD CAME OUT TODAY.
"WANTED, FEMALE ROOMMATE,
NONSMOKER, NON-UGLY."
NICE.
YEAH?
I JUST FIGURED
AFTER LIVING WITH YOU
IT WOULD BE AN INTERESTING
CHANGE OF PACE
TO HAVE
A FEMALE ROOMMATE.
YOU KNOW? SOMEONE
I COULD LEARN FROM.
SOMEONE...
SOMEONE WHO'S DIFFERENT THAN ME
AND WHAT'S MORE DIFFERENT
THAN ME-- A GUY WHO'S NOT 19--
THAN, SAY, A GIRL WHO IS 19?
YEAH?
NOT JUST A HAT RACK, MY FRIEND.
PHEEBS, I HAVE
TO ASK YOU...
SHH! I'M SWAMPED RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE JUST
STARING INTO SPACE.
UM, I'M TRYING
TO MOVE THAT PENCIL.
THIS ONE?
IT WORKED!
PHEEBS. THIS WHOLE
APARTMENT THING
IS A NIGHTMARE.
EVERY PLACE THAT
I CAN AFFORD
COMES WITH A ROOMMATE
WHO IS A FREAK.
I MEAN, LOOK AT THIS.
"WANTED. FEMALE ROOMMATE.
NONSMOKER, NON-UGLY."
I MEAN, IT'S JUST
THAT THERE'S NOTHING.
THIS CITY IS FULL.
WAIT, NO,
LOOK AT THIS.
"TWO BEDROOM, TWO BATH,
MUST BE NONSMOKER.
SATAN WORSHIPERS OKAY."
OH, YEAH, BUT
IT'S ON THE GROUND FLOOR.
HEY.
RACHE, UH, YOU STILL
LOOKING FOR A PLACE?
YEAH, WHY?
OKAY, THERE'S THIS GUY, WARREN
FROM THE MUSEUM AND HE'S GOING
ON A DIG FOR LIKE TWO YEARS
AND HE'S GOT
THIS GREAT PLACE
HE NEEDS TO SUBLET,
SO, UH... YOU INTERESTED?
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I'D LOVE TO LIVE AT WARREN'S.
I LOVE WARREN.
THANK YOU.
DON'T THANK ME.
YOU WANT TO THANK SOMEONE,
THANK THE VOLCANO
THAT ERUPTED THOUSANDS
OF YEARS AGO
KILLING,
BUT PERFECTLY PRESERVING
AN ENTIRE
CIVILIZATION.
HERE'S WARREN'S NUMBER.
OH, THIS IS GREAT.
I AM GOING TO CALL HIM
RIGHT NOW!
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
YOU GO CALL HIM.
I SAW IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
UM, I'M TALKING ABOUT THAT
WHICH YOU ALREADY KNOW
BUT WON'T ADMIT.
YOU KNOW,
THAT YOU LOVE HER AGAIN.
YOU RE-LOVE HER.
LOOK, I DO NOT RE-LOVE HER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WON'T JUST ADMIT IT.
OKAY, JUST PROMISE ME THAT
YOU WON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID.
LOOK, WE'RE JUST
FRIENDS NOW, OKAY?
WHY WOULD I DO ANYTHING STUPID?
( growling )
WELL, THE APARTMENT
IS ALREADY SUBLETTED.
THIS IS JUST HOPELESS.
I'M NEVER GOING
TO FIND ANYTHING.
YOU CAN LIVE WITH ME.
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I WOULD LOVE TO LIVE
WITH YOU, ROSS.
TH-THAT'S GREAT. THANK YOU.
I-I'M JUST GLAD I COULD,
YOU KNOW, HELP YOU OUT.
WOW, I'M,
I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU GUYS.
THIS IS SO, SO NOT STUPID.
ROSS, ROSS, YOU HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT THIS MEANS TO ME
I MEAN, I MEAN
I WAS GOING TO BE HOMELESS.
YOU'VE JUST SAVED ME.
YOU'RE MY HERO.
HERO. I, I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
OH, I HAVE TO GO
TELL MONICA
WHAT A WONDERFUL
BROTHER SHE HAS.
OH, PLEASE...
YOU'RE GOING TO SAY THINGS
NOW, AREN'T YOU?
NO. NO, I WON'T
BUT I SHOULD TELL YOU THIS:
THIS EXACT SAME THING
HAPPENED TO MY ROOMMATE DENISE.
SHE MOVED IN WITH A GUY
WHO WAS SECRETLY MARRIED TO HER
AND HE SAID HE DIDN'T LOVE HER
BUT HE REALLY DID
AND IT JUST BLEW UP
AND THAT'S HOW SHE ENDED UP
LIVING WITH ME.
OKAY, THAT'S A LIE.
HI.
HI, LISTEN, I'M SORRY
ABOUT BEFORE.
I DON'T NEED TO HAVE
A GAME ROOM.
I MEAN, WHEN I WAS A KID
I ONLY PLAYED THOSE GAMES
BECAUSE I COULDN'T
GET GIRLS
AND NOW I
CAN GET 'EM.
NOW I HAVE YOU.
NO,-N-NOT THAT I THINK
I HAVE YOU...
OR THINK OF YOU AS PROPERTY
IN ANY SORT OF WAY.
I SEE WOMEN...
STOP IT, CHANDLER.
I'M SORRY, TOO.
REALLY?
YEAH. OH, YES...
LISTEN, WE
DON'T HAVE
TO MAKE THAT
A GUEST ROOM.
WE CAN THINK
OF SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THE
ROOM TOGETHER.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WE CAN EASILY
THINK OF A WAY
FOR US BOTH
TO ENJOY THE ROOM.
TOTALLY.
WE DON'T HAVE
TO COME UP
WITH THIS NOW.
OH, GOOD.
HEY, WHY DON'T WE
THINK ABOUT CHANGES
WE CAN MAKE
IN THE LIVING ROOM.
CHANGES?
YEAH, I MEAN,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO MOVE AROUND
SOME FURNITURE
TO MAKE ROOM
FOR MY CHAIR.
Y-Y-YOU'RE GOING TO BRING
THE BARCALOUNGER OVER HERE?
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
WELL... IT'S JUST
THAT THEY'RE A SET
AND THEY SHOULD PROBABLY
STAY TOGETHER.
OH, THAT'S COOL.
THEN I'LL JUST, UH,
BRING THEM BOTH OVER.
SEE, NOW, NOW, YOU'RE TAKING
THEM AWAY FROM THEIR HOME.
OKAY. I GET IT.
SO I GET NOTHING.
NOTHING HERE IS MINE.
EVERYTHING IS YOURS.
I'LL GET UP IN THE MORNING
PUT ON YOUR CLOTHES,
AND HEAD OFF TO WORK.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YEAH, THAT'S IT--
EVERYTHING WILL BE MINE.
NOTHING WILL BE YOURS.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
COME ON, I'M TALKING
ABOUT THE BARCALOUNGER!
IT JUST, IT DOESN'T MATCH.
WHERE IS IT GOING TO GO?
IN THE GAME ROOM!
LOOK, IT IS NOT MY FAULT
THAT YOUR CHAIRS
ARE INCREDIBLY UGLY.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S
FINE. THAT'S FINE.
I WON'T BRING
THE CHAIRS.
ANYTHING.
I WOULDN'T WANT
TO RUIN THE AMBIANCE
OVER HERE AT GRANDMA'S PLACE!
EVERYTHING ON
YOUR APPLICATION
LOOKS REALLY GOOD. UH...
OH, JUST ONE LAST QUESTION.
UH...
ARE YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
GOING TO BE OVER HERE
ALL THE TIME LIKE PARTYING
AND HANGING OUT?
OH, DON'T WORRY,
I'M NOT REALLY A PARTY GIRL.
WHOA. NOW, LOOK.
DON'T JUST BE
BLURTING STUFF OUT.
I WANT YOU TO REALLY
THINK ABOUT YOUR ANSWERS.
( door opening )
YOU CAN CALL OFF
THE ROOMMATE SEARCH.
HI. I'LL BE LIVING HERE.
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
HE'S JUST SOME GUY WHO
REALLY WANTS THE APARTMENT
BUT I DON'T THINK
HE'S GOING TO GET IT.
WHY DID YOU TAKE THE
SHOWER CURTAIN DOWN?
THAT THING WAS A HAZARD.
I'M VERY SAFETY-CONSCIOUS.
HEY.
OH, I WAS JUST CLEARING
SOME SPACE FOR YOUR STUFF.
OH, THANKS.
BUT, LISTEN,
I WAS JUST AT MONICA'S
AND SHE AND CHANDLER
HAD A BIG FIGHT
AND THEY'RE NOT MOVING IN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
THEY'RE NOT MOVING IN?
THEY'RE-THEY'RE
STILL MOVING IN, RIGHT?
NO, NO. THEY JUST HAD
A BIG BLOWOUT
OVER WHAT TO DO WITH MY ROOM.
WHAT? OVER A STUPID ROOM?
I KNOW.
I FEEL KIND OF BAD FOR THEM
BUT I'M ALSO REALLY PSYCHED
'CAUSE NOW I DON'T HAVE
TO MOVE IN HERE.
OH. NO-NO, YEAH.
NO, THAT PART'S GREAT.
WHAT'S ALL THIS
ABOUT YOU GUYS FIGHTING?
IS THIS REALLY OVER A ROOM?
I MEAN, THAT IS SO SILLY.
ROSS, WE CAN HANDLE THIS.
UH, APPARENTLY NOT
AND I CAN'T JUST STAND BY
AND WATCH TWO PEOPLE
I CARE ABOUT SO MUCH BE HURT
BY SOMETHING THAT IS SO SILLY.
I MEAN
ENOUGH OF THE SILLINESS.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
TELL HER TO STOP BEING SILLY?
( babbling )
ALL RIGHT, OKAY, OKAY.
TWO VERY GOOD POINTS.
LOOK... I'VE KNOWN YOU BOTH
A LONG TIME
AND I'VE NEVER SEEN
EITHER OF YOU ONE-MILLIONTH
AS HAPPY AS YOU'VE BEEN
SINCE YOU GOT TOGETHER.
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO THROW
THAT ALL AWAY OVER A ROOM?
THAT IS SO SILLY.
I MEAN, WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT--
LOVE... OR SILLINESS?
WELL, WE ARE FOND
OF THE SILLINESS
BUT WE ALSO HAVE
A SOFT SPOT FOR THE LOVE.
LOVE IS THE BEST MEDICINE.
THAT'S LAUGHTER.
WHY DO YOU DO IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
NOW, CHANDLER, YOU WANT TO LIVE
WITH MONICA, RIGHT?
YEAH, I DO.
AND, MON, YOU WANT TO LIVE
WITH CHANDLER, DON'T YOU?
YES.
GOOD. A VERBAL CONTRACT
IS BINDING
IN THE STATE OF NEW YORK.
SO, I UNDERSTAND
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A PLACE.
NO, NO, I'M STAYING PUT.
OH.
I WAS GOING TO OFFER YOU
MY APARTMENT.
WHY? WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
HEY... RACH.
HI.
WELL, YOU'RE NEVER
GOING TO BELIEVE IT.
UM, MONICA AND CHANDLER
ARE MOVING IN AGAIN.
IT'S GREAT NEWS, RIGHT?
I MEAN, FOR THEM, RIGHT?
OH, WOW.
YEAH, BUT ON THE
BRIGHT SIDE, WE GET
TO BE ROOMMATES AGAIN.
YE... YEAH.
YOU KNOW, ABOUT THAT, UM...
ROSS, I... I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOUR OFFER
TO LET ME MOVE IN
AND EVERYTHING, BUT...
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE WEIRD?
WH-WHY?
WHY-WHY WOULD IT--
WHY WOULD IT BE WEIRD?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE OF US--
BECAUSE OF OUR HISTORY.
( high-pitched voice ):
NO!
NO?
NO! NO!
IT WOULD ONLY BE WEIRD
IF WE WERE STILL
IN THAT PLACE.
I MEAN, ARE YOU
STILL IN THAT PLACE?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
GOOD. ME NEITHER.
SO IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
AND WE'RE JUST
TWO FRIENDS
WHO HAPPEN TO
BE ROOMMATES.
OKAY, BUT, ROSS
EVENTUALLY YOU AND I
ARE GOING TO BE DATING.
REALLY. WE ARE.
WELL, YEAH. I'M GOING
TO HAVE A BOYFRIEND
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
OHH.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF YOU THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY
WE'LL JUST WORK OUT
A SYSTEM.
YOU KNOW, IT'LL BE
LIKE IN COLLEGE.
I'LL HANG A HANGER ON THE DOOR
AND PUT A SIGN:
"COME BACK LATER.
I'M GETTING LUCKY."
( cackling )
YEAH, I DIDN'T
THINK OF THAT.
SO ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS
WHOLE MOVING IN THING?
I MEAN,
IT'S A REALLY BIG STEP.
AND WHAT'S THE RUSH?
( Chandler and Monica
laughing )
THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
HE'S BEING SILLY
BECAUSE HE KNOWS
THAT WE ENJOY THE SILLINESS.
NO, I'M-I'M
SERIOUS, OKAY?
I MEAN, THINK
ABOUT IT.
YOU MOVE IN
UH, YOU START FIGHTING
OVER STUPID GAME ROOMS.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
YOU BREAK UP.
ROSS, YOU WERE RIGHT BEFORE.
IT WAS JUST A STUPID FIGHT
ABOUT A ROOM.
LOOK, THERE ARE
NO STUPID FIGHTS.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT THE ROOM.
THIS IS
ABOUT WHAT THE ROOMREPRESENTS
AND UNFORTUNATELY,
THIS ROOM COULD DESTROY YOU.
YEAH, I'M NOT SO WORRIED.
YEAH. NO, ME NEITHER.
FINE. IT'S YOUR LIFE.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOU GUYS BREAK UP, YOU KNOW?
WHICH YOU WILL DO
IF YOU MOVE IN TOGETHER.
BUT IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
DON'T DO IT!
YOU STILL WANT TO MOVE
IN TOGETHER, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
ROSS DIDN'T SCARE YOU?
SCARED ME OUT OF EVER
WANTING TO LIVE WITH HIM.
HEY, COME HERE.
I GOT TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
SOMEONE'S KILLED
SQUARE MAN.
THIS IS WHERE I THOUGHT
THE BARCALOUNGER COULD GO.
YOU SEE, YOU
CAN SEE THE TV
AND STILL, IT'S
WALKING DISTANCE
TO THE KITCHEN.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
I WANT TO SHOW
YOU SOMETHING, TOO.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW THOSE
BIG, BIG ROAD SIGNS
THAT SAY "MERGE"?
MM-HMM.
YOU KNOW?
SO I WAS THINKING
THAT WE COULD GET
ONE OF THOSE SIGNS
AND HANG IT OVER OUR BED...
BECAUSE
THAT'S YOU AND I TOGETHER.
"MERGE."
OH, MY GOD, I LOVE THAT.
REALLY?
UH, NO.
♪ I FOUND YOU IN MY BED ♪
♪ HOW'D YOU WIND UP THERE? ♪
♪ YOU ARE A MYSTERY ♪
♪ LITTLE BLACK CURLY HAIR ♪
♪ LITTLE BLACK, LITTLE BLACK,
LITTLE BLACK, LITTLE BLACK ♪
♪ LITTLE BLACK CURLY HAIR. ♪
( applause )
THANK YOU.
UM... NOW
IF YOU WANT TO RECEIVE E-MAILS
ABOUT MY UPCOMING SHOWS
THEN PLEASE GIVE ME MONEY
SO I CAN BUY A COMPUTER.
SO, UH...
( clearing throat )
WHERE ARE THE OTHER GUYS?
UM, WELL, LET'S SEE.
MONICA AND CHANDLER
ARE OCCUPIED.
FIGHTING?
NO, THE OTHER THING.
I REALLY THINK IT'S GREAT
THEY WORKED THINGS OUT.
YEAH, THERE'S NO BREAKING
THEM UP, IS THERE?
HEY, CAN I BORROW
THE KEY TO YOUR HOUSE
SO I CAN RUN ACROSS THE
STREET AND MAKE A COPY?
SURE. HERE.
THANK YOU.
NOW, ARE YOU SURE?
BECAUSE ONCE I MAKE A COPY,
THERE'S NO TURNING BACK.
YEAH, I'M SURE.
NOW, GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE I CHANGE MY MIND.
( Rachel laughing )
UH...
LISTEN, ROSS...
YOU REALLY THINK
THIS MOVING IN WITH RACHEL
IS A GOOD IDEA?
I'VE BEEN BACK AND FORTH.
YEAH, WELL, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD GO BACK, OKAY?
RACHEL MOVES IN
AND, BEFORE YOU KNOW IT
YOU'RE RIGHT WHERE
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE--
BACK TOGETHER.
YEAH, I DON'T THINK SO.
SHE'S ALREADY TALKING
ABOUT, YOU KNOW
DATING OTHER GUYS.
THAT'S NOT GOING
TO WORK OUT.
THEN SHE'S GOING
TO COME HOME ALL WEEPY
AND YOU'LL BE TELLING HER,
"OH, THAT'S OKAY.
YOU'LL FIND SOMEONE."
AND THEN BAM! SHE FINDS YOU.
WOW...
WELL, MAYBE
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM TELLING YOU, ROSS,
SHE IS DEFINITELY GOING
TO FALL IN LOVE
WITH YOU AGAIN.
NOW, IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
AW, IS THAT WHAT I WANT.
( loudly over microphone):
YES.
OKAY, HOLD ON. I'M GOING
TO MAKE YOUR LIFE MUCH EASIER.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
THE PLACE WAS CLOSED.
I'LL JUST COPY
IT LATER.
OR NOT.
WELL, RACH, WHY DON'T
YOU JUST MOVE IN WITH ME?
Ross:
OH, WHOA
WHOA, JOEY.
OH, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, LOOK, RACH,
I KNOW I SCARED YOU OFF
WITH THAT WHOLE
NAKED THURSDAYS THING, BUT...
WE DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
WELL... IT WOULD BE EASIER TO
MOVE JUST RIGHT ACROSS THE HALL.
WAIT A MINUTE--
UNLESS YOU'RE THINKING
ABOUT NAKED WEDNESDAYS.
THURSDAY'S CLEARLY
NOT GOOD FOR YOU.
PICK A DAY.
( scoffs )
HI. COME ON IN.
HI.
THANKS FOR
COMING BACK.
UM, THERE'VE BEEN
A LOT OF PEOPLE
INTERESTED IN THE ROOM,
BUT I HAVE NARROWED IT DOWN
AND YOU ARE ONE
OF THE FINALISTS.
GREAT.
OKAY, NOW,
BEFORE I MAKE MY DECISION
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT OUR PERSONALITIES
MATCH, OKAY?
SO I MADE UP A LITTLE TEST.
NOW, I'M GOING TO SAY A WORD
AND THEN YOU SAY THE FIRST
THING THAT COMES TO MIND.
I CAN DO THAT.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
PILLOW.
FIGHT.
VERY GOOD.
"G."
STRING?
EXCELLENT.
OKAY
UM...
DOGGIE.
KITTEN?
OOH, SORRY.
( making irritated
sound )
NO, NO, SO CLOSE, THOUGH
BUT, YOU KNOW, OKAY, BYE-BYE.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]